## A. Rizwan

## innovativewebpage@gmail.com

5.5 Years of experience in the field of software industry and has been worked appreciably on different projects. As part of assignments, I have been in Requirement Analysis, Design, Coding, Testing and support activities. Has good knowledge in REACT, EXPRESS, MONGODB, JAVASCRIPT, JAVASCRIPT ES6 and experience in Bootstrap 3, Codelgniter, PHP, OOPS, AJAX, Mysql and JQUERY technologies. .Has been productive self-starter with a strong work ethic, consistently achieve goals.

Experience	
MERN Stack Developer Ilife Technogies Pvt Ltd, Trichy	Mar 2021 - Sep 2022
MERN Stack Developer Beats Jobs Pvt Ltd, Chennai (India)	Aug 2019 - Aug 2020
VernalSoftPvt, Chennai, IN	Sep 2018 - Apr 2019
<b>Designer</b> Ilife Technologies	Jun 2014 - Aug 2018
Skills & Specialisation	
React, Mongodb, Php, Node.js, Jquery, Javascript, Express.js, Codeigniter, Html5, Css3	
Education	
BOARD/INSTITUTE Bharathidasan University Trichy, IN	
Jamal Mohamed College	Jan 2012
Websites	

www.bookade.com